[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Blazing Saddles, one the thugs that had to destroy Rock Ridge was shot for which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Chewing gum in line", "incorrect_answers": ["Smoking a cigar", "Having no criminal record", "Not bringing a gun with him"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2009 movie Drag Me to Hell stars Alison Lohman and Justin Long.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the usual color of the flowers of the peach tree?", "correct_answer": "Pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Yellow", "White"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the author of the spy thrillers The Bourne Identity, The Bourne Supremacy and The Bourne Ultimatum, which were adapted into movies starring Matt Damon.", "correct_answer": "Robert Ludlum", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert J. Sawyer", "Robert Kerr", "Robert Coover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What author is not correctly matched with the literary work he created?", "correct_answer": "Alan Alexander Milne - The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", "incorrect_answers": ["Alexander Pushkin - Eugene Onegin", "Alexander Pope - The Rape of the Lock", "Alexandre Dumas, p\u00e8re - The Count of Monte Cristo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Peter Fonda play in the 2007 film Ghost rider?", "correct_answer": "Mephistopheles", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny Blaze", "Blackheart", "Barton Blaze"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the mysterious murderer from the urban legend known as The Babysitter and the Man Upstairs?", "correct_answer": "A madman", "incorrect_answers": ["The father of the children", "The babysitters boyfriend", "The neighbor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A speeder caught by photo radar, sends the police a photograph of money to pay his fine.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the hit movie from the 80s Raging Bull?", "correct_answer": "Martin Scorcese", "incorrect_answers": ["Stanley Kubrick", "Francis Ford Coppolla", "George Lucas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What band released Bitter Sweet Symphony on 16 June, 1997 as the first single from their third album Urban Hymns?", "correct_answer": "The Verve", "incorrect_answers": ["Blink-182", "Blur", "Foo Fighters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What port on the Atlantic Ocean is the capital and largest city of Guinea.", "correct_answer": "Conakry", "incorrect_answers": ["Baku", "Dhaka", "Bujumbura"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cultivated on a huge scale for the brewery industry, this plant grows separate as male and female.", "correct_answer": "Hops", "incorrect_answers": ["Yeast", "Amber", "Rockberry"]}]